Zohan Subhash

Kochi, Kerala, India



zohan.subhash@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/zobro23

Summary

I'm a freshman in highschool, and I code in my free time. I'm a self-taught software programmer, focusing primarily on backend development with NodeJS. I'm open to new technologies though, and I enjoy trying out new languages and new fields, from software testing to workflow automation. I've even worked as a customer support agent for some time! I do open-source contributions too, and these can be found on my GitHub profile (see featured links). In short, software and technology excite me, and I love programming

Experience



Software Developer

Entice Institute

Oct 2021 - Present (1 year 1 month +)

Entice Institute manages clinicalguruji.com, offering online courses for medical students and professionals

- Built webhooks to trigger Whatsapp API for task automation
- This enabled automatic-invoicing, Whatsapp promotions, payment update notifications, and Whatsapp OTP verification
- Resulted in frictionless customer support and enhanced sales of new courses

fi Software Engineer

Fiverr

Oct 2021 - Feb 2022 (5 months)

Fiverr is a freelancing platform for software development services

- Built a Discord bot to remotely trigger jobs on a server https://github.com/Zo-Bro-23/batch-file-bot
- Wrote a tutorial to make your own Discord bot https://zobro23.medium.com/discord-js-tutorial-affdf8fc1718
- Built a Discord bot to host and manage role-playing games
- Built the backend framework for an e-commerce application
- Wrote documentation for a REST API
- Built a Telegram bot to add and remove users based on merit points awarded by other users

Senior Software Tester

SHAZAMME

Nov 2021 - Jan 2022 (3 months)

Shazamme is an online recruitment website

- Built automated testing scripts using the puppeteer framework
- These scripts helped in uncovering numerous bugs and enabled a quality release

- Performed load testing to ensure the system holds up during high traffic scenarios

Technical Support Specialist

Directly

Aug 2021 - Oct 2021 (3 months)

Directly is a customer service platform for Microsoft and other companies

- Worked as a Windows Expert Advisor to troubleshoot issues reported by Microsoft customers
- Handled 159 customer issues
- Earnt 22 customer satisfaction badges

Education

Johns Hopkins Center For Talented Youth (CTY)

Honors Chemistry, Honors Biology, AP Biology, AP English Lang Jul 2021 - Mar 2023

Homeschool

Schooling Apr 2020 - Jul 2023

Art of Problem Solving

AP Calculus BC Aug 2022 - Mar 2023

Pennsylvania Homeschoolers

AP Physics C (Mechanics + E&M), AP Microeconomics Aug 2022 - Mar 2023

Khan Academy

High School Geometry, Algebra 2, Trigonometry, Precalculus Jun 2022 - Aug 2022

Choice School

Schooling
Jun 2011 - Mar 2020

Skills

Software Development • Video Editing • JavaScript • Media Production • Customer Support • Git • Python (Programming Language) • REST • Automated Software Testing • MongoDB and PostgreSQL